globester.com 2007-06-01

# Globester Travel-Airline Consolidator for Discount International Airfares, Cheap Flights and Ticket deals to Europe, Africa, Middle-East, Asia, Australia, New Zealand, South America and Central America

|   
  
Globester's Privacy Policy and YOU

Welcome to the Privacy Policy page of the [www.globester.com](http://www.globester.com/) website. We encourage you to read the entire contents as we understand that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part; we take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of your personal information

As a valued and respected customer of the www.globester.com web site, we recognize the importance of **protecting your personal information** with the highest standards and best practices of organizations doing business on the Internet. We are always conscious of your personal privacy when you transact with us.

This **Privacy Policy** describes the practices that apply to the www.gobester.com web site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information, and what we do with that information. Here are the FACTS: 

  * We will NOT collect personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number ("Personal Information") without your **knowledge and permission**  

  * We will allow you to view, correct or remove your Personal Information and other information associated with your registration as a user of our site   

  * We will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect from you. 

  |   
So, what Information do we collect? |    
  |    
We collect your personal information when you - 

  * Become an www.globester.com member 
  * Complete a traveler profile 
  * Purchase travel 
  * Participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes 
  * Contact www.globester.com 

  |   
Member information |    
  
www.globester.com collects your Member/User ID, password, and e-mail address when you register to become a member of our web site.   
  
  |   
Traveler profile information |    
  
www.globester.com collects your full name and contact number when a travel reservation is made. We also collect information about your preferences, including meal requests, seat selection, frequent flyer/hotel/car rental programs and membership numbers, and ticketing options.

When someone other than yourself is accompanying you on travel purchased through www.globester.com, we may collect their personal information and travel preferences. You should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing www.globester.com with their full names, contact numbers, e-mail addresses, and travel preferences, as they will be unable to directly access our systems to view or change any information you provide on their behalf.  
  
  |   
Travel purchase information  |    
  
www.globester.com collects the billing address of the credit card that is used to purchase travel. We will also collect credit card information, including card number, card type, cardholder name, and expiration date, in order to bill you for travel purchased through our secure web site. Please view our Credit Card Guarantee for additional information on www.globester.com's commitment to protecting your credit card security.  
  
  |   
Contests and sweepstakes information  |    
  
Occasionally, www.globester.com may offer you and other site visitors an opportunity to participate in a contest or sweepstakes. Information collected by www.globester.com when you participate in a contest or sweepstakes may include your full name, e-mail address, phone number and street address.  
  
  |   
Surveys |    
  
www.globester.com may offer you and other site visitors an opportunity to participate in surveys regarding your experience with our site. For our members, we may also send these surveys via e-mail. You are under no obligation to respond to any survey, and you may unsubscribe from receiving these e-mail surveys by following the unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail survey you receive. Information collected by www.globester.com when you participate in a survey may include your full name, e-mail address, phone number and street address.  
  
  |   
Contacting www.globester.com |    
  
www.globester.com your full name, Member ID, e-mail address, and/or contact number whenever you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with viewing your itinerary, logging on to www.globester.com, or accessing your account.   
  
  |   
Cookies |    
  
A cookie is a small file stored on your computer's hard drive, which is used to enhance your visit to www.globester.com and provide you with information tailored to your needs. It stores user preference information, keeps track of a purchase transaction during a session on www.globester.com, and enhances site security. For instance, cookies allow you to visit pages within a site without having to reintroduce yourself. 

You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about cookie functions. Be advised that, by refusing to accept a cookie, you will not be able to access many travel services and planning tools offered by www.globester.com. 

In addition, when you arrive at or leave the www.globester.com web site, we automatically receive the web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our web site you visit while you are on the site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our web site. We use this information only to try to understand your preferences better and to manage the load on our servers, so as to improve our service and your experience with www.globester.com. We do not track the web sites that you visit before or after you leave our site.   
  
  |   
Sharing of Personal Information and Disclosure |    
  
www.globester.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

[www.globester.com ](http://www.globester.com/) only discloses your Personal Information to those travel providers that you decide to make arrangements with through our site. For example, when you purchase an airline ticket or book a hotel room or reserve a car, we will provide the airline, hotel or car rental agency, as the case may be, with the Personal Information needed to process your transaction. We use our reasonable efforts to ensure that these travel providers will also protect your Personal Information. We contract with other companies to perform various functions necessary to operate our business - for example, to deliver tickets, ship items and process credit cards. We will share with these other companies only that Personal Information they require to fulfill your orders. These companies agree that they will not use or disclose that Personal Information for any other purpose.  
  
  |   
  
* Over time, this policy can and will be revised as new features are added to the [www.globester.com ](http://www.globester.com/) web site and/or as we incorporate your valued suggestions and feedback. Thank you and have a SAFE journey!!   
  
  |
